seoworkers.com 2014-12-21

# SEO Workers Web Site Privacy Policy & Important Notices

**You are here:**

  * Home
  * Web Site Imprint, Privacy Policy & Important Notices

## SEO Workers Web Site Imprint, Privacy Policy & Important Notices

Thank you for visiting SEO Workers and reviewing our policy notices. We have integrated these statements into a single posting for ease of use.

The following links will help you navigate to a specific section:

  * SEO Workers Official Impressum for Privacy Related Matters.
  * Web Site Privacy Policy;
  * Automatically Collected Information;
  * Information Collected for Tracking and Customization (Cookies);
  * Personal Information;
  * Children’s Information;
  * Opt Out Policy;
  * Web Site Security Notice;
  * Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement;
  * Warranty and Disclaimer;
  * Reproduction of Articles and Tutorials;

* * *

* * *

### SEO Workers Official Impressum for Privacy Related Matters

According to § 2 DL-InfoV the following information is provided:

Helga Haas   
SEO Workers   
Willi-Stoer Str. 4  
D-86159 Augsburg  
Germany.

Telephone number: +49-821-4087363

Local Tax Identification Number: 103/174/22801  
International Tax Identification Number: DE283547288

Updated: September 25th, 2012.

Notice: The impressum above, also reflects to our Facebook company page <http://www.facebook.com/seoworkers>.

* * *

### Privacy Policy

This notice provides SEO Workers policy regarding the nature, purpose, use and sharing of any information collected via this Web site.

The information you provide on a SEO Workers Web site will be used only for its intended purpose. We will protect your information consistent with the principles of the German Privacy Act.

Submitting information is strictly voluntary. By doing so, you are giving SEO Workers your permission to use the information for the intended purpose.

If you do not want to give SEO Workers permission to use your information, simply do not provide it.

However, not providing certain information may result in SEO Workers inability to provide you with the information or services you desire.

There are several types of information we collect. These include:

  * Automatically Collected Information;
  * Information Collected for Tracking and Customization (Cookies);
  * Personal Information;
  * Children Information.

SEO Workers never collects information for commercial marketing. We will NEVER share your information with another government agency if it relates to that agency, or as otherwise required by law.

SEO Workers never creates individual profiles or gives your information to any private organization.

* * *

### Automatically Collected Information

We collect and temporarily store certain technical information about your visit for use in site management and security purposes. This information includes:

  * The Internet domain from which you access our Web site (for example, ’xcompany.com’ if you use a private Internet access account, or ’yourschool.edu’ if you connect from an educational domain);
  * The IP address (a unique number for each computer connected to the Internet) from which you access our Web site;
  * The type of browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) used to access our site;
  * The operating system (Windows, Unix) used to access our site;
  * The date and time you access our site;
  * The URLs of the pages you visit;
  * Your username, if it was used to log in to the Web site;
  * If you visited this SEO Workers Web site from another Web site, the URL of the forwarding site.

This information is only used to help us make our site more useful for you. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits.

Raw data logs are retained temporarily as required for security and site management purposes only.

* * *

### Information Collected for Tracking and Customization (Cookies)

A cookie is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer to allow it to remember specific information about your session while you are connected.

Your computer will only share the information in the cookie with the Web site that provided it, and no other Web site can request it. There are two types of cookies, session and persistent.

  * Session cookies last only as long as your Web browser is open. Once you close your browser, the cookie disappears.
  * Persistent cookies store information on your computer for longer periods of time.

SEO Workers Web sites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site.

A few SEO Workers Web sites may also make use of persistent cookies to remember you between visits so, for example, you can save your customized preference settings for future visits.

Each SEO Workers site using persistent cookies identifies itself as doing so.

Your private information, whether stored in persistent cookies or elsewhere, are only shared with the third party service of **Google, Inc.** and only for our use of their service called **"Google Analytics"** , but your IP address is not delivered to this third party website.

To provide website visitors more choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics, Google also have developed the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en "External web site"). The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics. 

If you want to opt-out, download and install the add-on for your current web browser. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is available for Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera.

If you do not wish to have any session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser. However, this may affect the functioning of some SEO Workers Web sites.

* * *

### Personal Information

SEO Workers sometimes gathers personal information from its users, through such methods as the user completing a form or sending us an e-mail

If you choose to provide us with personal information, we will use that information only to respond to your message and to help us give you the information or services you have requested.

Remember that e-mail isn’t necessarily secure. You should never send sensitive or personal information like your Social Security number or your Credit Card number in an e-mail. Use postal mail or secure Web sites instead.

Some of our Web sites ask visitors who request specific information to fill out a registration form.

For example, vendors looking for marketing opportunities by visiting our SEO Workers Acquisition Internet Service site may be asked to register to obtain e-mail notices of business opportunities.

Other information collected at Web sites through questionnaires, feedback forms, or other means, enables us to determine visitors’ interests, with the goal of providing better service to our customers.

* * *

### Children’s Information

The Children’s On-line Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) governs information gathering online from or about children under the age of 13.

Verifiable consent from a child’s parent or guardian is required before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from a child under the age of 13.

We collect no information about you or your child, other than that detailed in the previous section, when you visit our web site unless you choose to provide information to us.

When a SEO Workers Web site needs to collect information about a child under 13 years old, COPPA required information and instructions will be provided by the specific Web page that collects information about the child.

The Web page will specify exactly what the information will be used for, who will see it, and how long it will be kept.

There are several exceptions that permit collection of a child’s e-mail address without receiving parental consent in advance:

To provide the parents with notice and to seek consent for communications with the child.

Note: this may require collection of the parent’s e-mail address as well.

To respond to a one time request from a child. To respond more than once to a child’s request; i.e., subscription to a newsletter. However, parental consent is required prior to the second communication:

  * To protect the safety of a child who is participating on the site; i.e., in a chat room;
  * To protect the site or to respond to law enforcement; i.e., in the case of a Web site compromise.

Personal information about children under 13 years of age may be needed to respond to his/her communication to us, such as to receive a poster or to acquire information for a school project.

Personal information about your child will be destroyed immediately upon completion of its intended purpose.

On rare occasions, it may be determined that a communication from a child under 13 years old should be maintained for historical purposes.

Should such an occasion occur, SEO Workers will obtain the necessary consent from the child’s parent.

Finally, we provide many on-line tools and services in support of SEO Workers’ mission.

A child under 13 years old may inadvertently provide personal information to one of these services. If this should happen, the information about the child will be deleted immediately upon discovery.

* * *

### Opt Out Policy

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You also can send mail to the following postal address:

**SEO Workers**   
Helga Haas, CEO   
Will-Stoer Str. 4,   
D-86159 Augsburg,   
Bavaria   
Germany.

You can call one of the following telephone:

**Germany:** +49-821-4087363   
**United States:** : +1-323-580-6285    
**United Kingdom:** +44-20-3286-0213   
**Australia:** +61-3-9016-3603

* * *

### Web Site Security Notice

For site security purposes and to ensure that this Web service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs that monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information.

Anyone using this system expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that if such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials.

Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information on SEO Workers servers are strictly prohibited and may be punishable by law.

* * *

### Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement

SEO Workers links to many Web sites created and maintained by other public and/or private organizations. SEO Workers provides links to these sites as a service to our users.

The presence of a link is not a SEO Workers endorsement of the site.

When users follow a link to an outside Web site, they are leaving SEO Workers and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside Web site(s).

SEO Workers is not responsible for the information collection practices of non-SEO Workers sites.

* * *

### Warranty and Disclaimer

SEO Workers web site, services and materials, are provided by SEO Workers under these terms of use "as is" without warranty of any kind, either express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of title, non-infringement, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.

Without limiting the foregoing, SEO Workers makes no warranty that

  1. the site, services or materials will meet your requirements;
  2. the site, services or materials will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error-free;
  3. the results that may be obtained from the use of the site, services or materials will be effective, accurate, or reliable;
  4. the quality of the site or any services or materials purchased or accessible by you will meet your expectations;
  5. any errors or defects in the site, services or materials will be corrected.

This site, services and materials may include technical or other mistakes, inaccuracies, or typographical errors.

SEO Workers may make changes to the site, materials and services, including the prices and descriptions of any software or products listed, at any time in its sole discretion and without notice.

The site, materials and services may be out of date, and SEO Workers makes no commitment to update the site, materials and services.

* * *

### Reproduction of Articles and Tutorials

SEO Workers retains full copyrights to all materials published by them on this site. None of the material published on this site may be used, in part or in whole, in any medium whatsoever, by any entity outside of SEO Workers.
